(radio screeching)
- [Radio Host]
You don't have to forget
Just remember this
Sunday, all right
(upbeat instrumental music)
♪♪♪
♪ There's times where
I want something more ♪
♪ Someone more like me ♪
♪ There's times when this dress
rehearsal seems incomplete ♪
♪ But you see the colors
in me like no one else ♪
♪ And behind your
dark glasses you're ♪
♪ You're something else ♪
♪ You're really lovely ♪
♪ Underneath it all ♪
♪ You want to love me ♪
♪ I'm really lucky ♪
♪ Underneath it all ♪
♪ You're really lovely ♪
♪ You know some
real bad tricks ♪
♪ And you need some discipline ♪
♪ But lately you've
been trying real hard ♪
♪ And giving me your best ♪
♪ And you give me the
most gorgeous sleep ♪
♪ That I've ever had ♪
♪ And when it's really bad
I guess it's not that bad ♪
♪ You're really lovely ♪
♪ Underneath it all ♪
♪ You want to love me ♪
♪ I'm really lucky ♪
♪ Underneath it all ♪
♪ You're really lovely ♪
♪ So many moons
that we have seen ♪
♪ Stumbling back next to me ♪
♪ I've seen right
through and underneath ♪
♪ And you make me better ♪
♪ I've seen right
through and underneath ♪
♪ And you make me better ♪
♪ Better, better ♪
♪ For real ♪
♪ 'Cause underneath it all ♪
♪ You are my real
prince charming ♪
♪ Like the heat from the fire ♪
♪ You are always burning ♪
♪ Anytime you're around ♪
♪ My body keeps calling ♪
♪ For your touch, your kisses
and your sweet romance ♪
♪ There's an underside of you ♪
♪ That this here woman adore ♪
♪ Aside from your temper
everything is secure ♪
♪ You're good for me, baby ♪
♪ Of that I'm sure ♪
♪ 'Cause over and over
again I want more ♪
♪ You've used up
all your coupons ♪
♪ And all you've
got left is me ♪
♪ And somehow I'm
full of forgiveness ♪
♪ I guess it's meant to be ♪
♪ You're really lovely ♪
♪ Underneath it all ♪
♪ You want to love me ♪
♪ I'm really lucky ♪
♪ Underneath it all ♪
♪ You're really lovely ♪
♪ Um um um ♪
♪ Underneath it all ♪